

# Berk Disli

# Full Stack Web Developer

# **Profile**

Passionate full stack developer, trained in back-end and front-end development. Experienced in engineering and social media industries. Skilled at designing, web development, debugging and modifying websites, apps and mobile applications.

Linkedin - GitHub - Portfolio - Medium

Education

Aug 2021 — Mar 2022

Berlin/Germany

CareerFoundry

Full Stack Web Development program that helps student develop skills in API, web and mobile applications. Provides hands on experience designing and building databases for software applications, creating and deploying web API, securing and managing user authentication and deploying web applications to the cloud. <u>Link</u> to the detailed curriculum of the

program.

Sep 2011 — Jun 2016

Istanbul/Turkey

Isik University

Biomedical Engineering

Program covers fundamental topics of electrical and electronics engineering along with core biomedical engineering courses on systems, physiology, biomaterials, biomechanics, bioinstrumentation, bio-signal processing, medical imaging and

bioinformatics.

Skills

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Angular

Redux

React Native

jQuery

Node.js

MongoDB

Jest

# Development Projects

# Web and Mobile Applications

#### Pokédex API: List of Pokémons

• The web application is designed to provide an overview of all the Pokémon characters.

Tools: jQuery, Bootstrap

#### **Chit-Chat: A chat app**

• Chit-Chat is a mobile application for fast communication between end users.

Tools: React Native, Expo, GiftedChat, NetInfo

**To-Do-List App** 

# Languages

English

German

Turkish

• A basic to-do-list app allowing users to add and delete to-dos, edit and mark them as completed.

Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

# Meet App: List of developers' events

• The web application is used to see the upcoming events which are set up in Google Calendar.

Tools: React, Jest, Google Calendar API

#### **Movie App: MyFlix**

 The website is designed to show the retrieved film data and enable a user profile section. Functions such as logging in, logging out, registering and de-registering users are also integrated.

**Tools**: React, React-Bootstrap, Netlify, MongoDB, Angular

# **Employment History**

### Social Media Specialist, Majorel, Berlin 01.2021 - present

- Responsible for evaluating online social media content (images, videos, text, etc.), showed in the social media app
- Removal of inappropriate content in order to ensure a safe experience for users of the application and community
- · Maintain a high level of quality in each case

### Social Media Specialist, Conectys, Istanbul 11.2018 - 02.2020

- Screened, monitored, and approved social media content
- Moderated videos, audio clips and comments within the German market for a well-known company

# Field Service Engineer, Medisa, Istanbul 01.2016 - 11.2016

- Designed, tested and implemented new medical procedures as well as modified products, equipment and devices
- Trained staff to use equipment safely and properly
- · Wrote technical reports and documentation